(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T08:55:43.317959",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日の3Dお披露目は…
Today's 3D showcase is...
Raora makes her 3D debut!!
Raora Arrives at Chattini Land, and...
Unleashes Chaos in Mini-Games for a Jetpack!
Tears!
Please give me the ticket!!
Rage!
I'm done!!!!
Sexy?
Songs!
Unexpected Fights?!
Can she get the Jetpack?!
Ciao, Raora!
Are you recording me?
How do I look? How do I look?
What is this place?
Oh my gosh!
That's a... That's a giant Chattina and castle!
And look at the one in the fountain, and the plush shop over there, and there's another one over there...
and another one over there! Wait a second!
Is this? Is this?
Is this Chattini Land?!
That's so cool!
Ah, hey, hey, hey, hey, cameraman, come here, come here, come here, come here!
How do I look in 3D? Huh?
Hey, you should take a look too. You should take a look to my Chattino!
Look at him!
Isn't he so pretty?
So cute, right?
Ah, and you also should take a look too, my tail!
Big cat means big tail!
Ah, what do you think? How do I look?
Hey, Raora! Raora, Raora, Raora!
Hey! Hey! Whoa!
Chattino! What did you do?
Ah, come here now!
I'm gonna I'm gonna use my weapon!
Yeah, come here! Ah, now...
Wait a second!! I need to tell you something! How dare you! How dare you knock me off like this!
Huh? Hey? Hey, you can you can talk?
Oh, that's impressive.
Well, I'm guessing...
You need me for something? What do you need?
Yeah. There's this thing we want, but... The only way you can get it is by clearing all the Mini-Games here in Chattini Land!
Mini-games? Something you can only get here by clearing mini-games?
Hey, I think I know what it is.
It's... that thing over there!
Jetpack Chattini! I knew it is a jetpack!
Oh, the Chattini want one so badly, right?
We can't get it on our own, though, so help us out Raora! Please!
Ah, are you begging me?
Well, you know our little one? No.
I told you I'm not giving you the jetpack. So, I'm leaving. Bye-bye!
Please! Please! Pleeease!
Hey, are you following me?
Ah... Well, I guess it's a special day after all.
You know what? I'll give it a shot.
Yaaaay!
Ah, okay. Well, then, what should I do here?
The game's in this area of the land, so good luck!
Okay, then, you know what? I'm gonna do my very best!
Well, I should go then. Gambare, Raora! Raora!
Oh, wait. The right way is over there.
I mean...
Ah, I'm helping out. Ah, gambare, Raora! Raora!
提供 チャッティーニランド株式会社
Presented by Chattini Land Co., Ltd.
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん？
Staying pure until the end?
Love, bluh bluh bluh
Love, bluh bluh
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん?
Are you really gonna die as a virgin boy?
ラブと超（ちょう）ライク パーティションはない、ない
Loving and liking, they're just one and the same
きみだけが特別（とくべつ）じゃないんだ
You're not that special, it's just part of the game
反省（はんせい）とかあたしに求（もと）められても...
"Hey, I'm sorry" – is that really what you want to hear me say?
ほんと病（や）んだり勘違い（かんちがい）しないで で?で?で?
No way! Don't get all sick and depressed over this, okay?
どうしてなんで期待（きたい）の戸締（とじ）まり忘（わす）れるの?
Stop! Don't you know, never wanting any more is rule number one?
最初（さいしょ）にアレほどやめときなっていったじゃん
Right from the start not to give it any heart, it's only for fun
お純情（じゅんじょう）様（さま）、あちらが出口（でぐち）ですが...
Mr. commitment, you can find the exit over to the right
やっぱ帰（かえ）りたくないですか? ホップステップ
Oh my, are you really staying for the night?
う〜、ワンモアチャンス!
And one more chance!
もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん POPな愛撫（あいぶ）
So if it's appeal, keep it real, baby shake that
謳（うた）ったらいいじゃん みっともないから嫉妬（しっと）しまいな
Pop in a feel, and keep going like that
発火（はっか）しちゃうとかくっそダセェな 淋（さび）しくなったら誰（だれ）でもいいじゃん埋（う）まればいいじゃん
Don't be a creep, that's some weird jealousy
嫌々（いやいや）愛（あい）して生（い）きたくなって 死（し）ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん?
If you really want some, if you're feeling lonely, baby get lucky
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん BADなダンス 腫（しゅ）魔（ま）ったらいいじゃん
So if it's appeal, keep it real, baby shake that
やっぱり好きとかやってられんわ 馬鹿（ばか）じゃない? 咽喉（あー）くっそ雑（ぞう）雑（ざ）おえわ
Down with the feels? With a face screaming down bad?
淋（さび）しくなったら誰（だれ）でもいいじゃん 埋（う）まればいいじゃん 埋（う）まればいいじゃん
"Love you!" (I don't) Gross, I'm going limp
嫌々（いやいや）愛（あい）して死（し）にたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK? 「はーい」
Are you out of your mind? Ugh, you're such a simp!
Love, bluh bluh bluh
Love, bluh bluh
バーストからインスタントラヴァー 頭（あたま）＋身体（からだ）がバカに絡（から）まらあ
Bursting rubber, we're instant lovers and under the covers, we smother each other
ゴーストならアンデッドマナー ああ未（いま）だ淫（みだ）ら
Ghost or not, it's undead manners, come dear, you gotta...
今際（いまわ）火花（ひばな）散（ち）らばそれがアンサー、だ
Right? And one more chance!
バーストからインスタントラヴァー 頭（あたま）＋身体（from）がバカに絡（から）まらあ
Bursting rubber, we're instant lovers and under the covers, we smother each other
ゴーストならアンデッドマナー ああ未（いま）だ淫（みだ）ら 今際（いまわ）火花（ひばな）散（ち）らばそれがアンサー、だ
Ghost or not, it's undead manners, right?
う〜、ワンモアチャンス! もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん POPな愛撫（あいぶ）
So if it's appeal, keep it real, baby shake that
謳（うた）ったらいいじゃん みっともないから嫉妬（しっと）しまいな
Pop in a feel, and keep going like that
発火（はっか）しちゃうとかくっそダセェな 淋（さび）しくなったら誰（だれ）でもいいじゃん埋（う）まればいいじゃん
Don't be a creep, that's some weird jealousy
嫌々（いやいや）愛（あい）して生（い）きたくなって 死（し）ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん?
If you really want some, if you're feeling lonely, baby get lucky
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん BADなダンス 腫（しゅ）魔（ま）ったらいいじゃん
So if it's appeal, keep it real, baby shake that
やっぱり好きとかやってられんわ 馬鹿（ばか）じゃない? 咽喉（あー）くっそ雑（ぞう）雑（ざ）おえわ
Down with the feels? With a face screaming down bad?
淋（さび）しくなったら誰（だれ）でもいいじゃん 埋（う）まればいいじゃん 埋（う）まればいいじゃん
"Love you!" (I don't) Gross, I'm going limp
嫌々（いやいや）愛（あい）して死（し）にたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK?
Are you out of your mind? Ugh, you're such a simp!
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん とっくのとうに終わったと思いだみっともないとか言ってごめんな
So if it's appeal, keep it real, baby shake that
発火したいけどもだめなんだ 淋しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん
How many years has it been since I felt like –
いやいや愛して生きたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK? 「はーい」
Sorry to call you a creep, that's on me I'm thirsty for love
やいやいやいや 悪（わる）い子（こ）さん
My my my, you're just a little freak
まあまあまあまあ お愛嬌（あいきょう）じゃん
Why why why, you're just the same as me
さあさあさあさあ 始（はじ）めるよ
Right right right, it's time to start the show
もっと この穴（あな）を 愛（あい）してよ
Once more, deeper into this rabbit hole we go
やいやいやいや 悪（わる）い子（こ）さん
My my my, you're just a little freak
まあまあまあまあ お愛嬌（あいきょう）じゃん
Why why why, you're just the same as me
さあさあさあさあ 始（はじ）めるよ
Right right right, it's time to start the show
もっと この穴（あな）を 愛（あい）してよだっせ
Once more, deeper into this rabbit hole we go, so gross!
Chattini Land Flower Garden Area
What Mini-Games Await Raora?!
Look at this place!
I was not expecting to play a game in such a pretty place.
And I wonder what kind of game is going to be...
Raora! This is your conscience?
My conscience? Do I have one?
Oh, Morii? Is that? Your turn.
Say something, say something.
Is that a dog?
It's not your sample!
Congrats, Raora, on your 3D debut!
We're so happy for you.
Thank you so much! I'm so happy to be here with you.
Yes, thank you!
No, you're cute! No, you're cute!
Well, as you may have assumed by our grand entrance over here, your opponents for this mini-game are, as you see...
Mori Calliope from hololive English -Myth-! If you don't know me, now you do. Who's over here?
Ouro Kronii from hololive English -Promise-!
And um, who could this beautiful woman be? Dare desu ka?
Yes, thank you. Uh, docchi-docchi?
Inugami Korone!
I came from hololive! Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! Thank you so much for coming today!
Thank you so much!
What kind of game are we going to play today?
Well, get ready because it's time for...
1, 2, 3, Stage!
Say Cheese! Raora!!
Excited?
Now then, here are the rules, Chattini...
are going to jump out of the bushes at random intervals to snap a photo of you.
And when they do so, you got to enter the frame and then strike a specific pose for them.
Okay, this sounds easy.
Like that, like that! Just move into the camera frame and strike the pose once Chattini jump out.
Okay, wait, wait.
And then it is... Is this a good example? Yeah, exactly!
She's a little too hyped for that.
Oh, I know! Pretty hard!
No, no, no, you have to be competitive. You have to be competitive in this game, yes.
And well, as you have seen, Raora clears it if she can pose 5 or more times at the designated location within the time limit!
To easy, right?
Too easy, right?
I got it!
It sounds super fun! Let's go!
Yeah, but it's not going to be easy.
Yeah, it's not going to be easy because we're going to be taking part as well,
And I'm going to get in your way. No, I'm going to get in your way! No, I'm going to get in your way!
I'm going to get in your way. Well, or so I think.
No, I'm going to get the ticket! I'm going to win!
Yes.
I guess that means we're all going to get each other super close.
Loser! Loser!
Raora, little loser!
No, I'm not a loser! You're a loser!
Yo, no, no, no.
Woah, I feel like I'm really confident now.
Confident? Not anymore!
Little too confident. No, don't worry, no, it's okay, it's all good, all good.
I'm striking a pose, it's a pose game! It's a pose game! Got it, got it, got it!
Are you guys excited? We're not excited?
Are you guys excited? We're excited!
Okay, if everybody's ready, then... okay, let's do this!
Let's do it!
Hope you're all ready troops! Are you guys excited?
Yeah!
Get ready to start voguing! Since it would be a shame to go straight into the real thing, let us do some practice first, okay?
Okay, okay, let's do it. All right, so here we go. Three, two, one,
start!
Test play start!
Okay, let's see. First camera. Here! Here, here, here! Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Points!
Oh, no, you're not going to step on me!
What is it? Yeah, yeah! No, no, no! No, no, no! Points! Okay, uh...
Okay, let's see. Next time. Yes, yes! This is Calli, oh, it's time to shine! Points!
One more! Hey, hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey! Points!
Where? Where, where, where? No, no, no! No, no! Away! Dammit!
Time's up!
You doing okay there, buddy? So good!
I will touch you, and I will hurt you. Just so we're all on the same page, I will hurt you if I have to.
Ha me! I love it! That's not the response I expected.
Well, then. Shall we move on to the main event, ladies?
Okay. Yes. Okay, the time limit for the main event is two minutes. Whoever strikes the right pose in the required spots most is the winner.
Now then, let's get this show on the road. Three, two, one, it is on!
Game start!
What is it? Yay! Points!
That was kind of nutty.
Let's go! Let's go! What is it? No, no, no, no, no! Points!
Let's go! Oh man, I'm going to get injured. No! Away! You hurt me! Missed!
Okay, next one is mine. What is it?
As I said, I will hurt you. No, no, no, no! Say cheese! No! Points!
Man, everyone's so good. I know. That you know, hurting each other. No, get it! No! Points!
What is it? No, no, no, no, no! No! No! Away! Points!
Time's up!
It's okay! It's okay! Ugh!
Come on!
Points!
Why is she so strong?
She's rejecting all of my pushes!
Button mash! Go!
Missed!
Okay...
Really blocking—
Oh!
Yeah!
Man, I'm not even gonna try on this one.
Points!
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Next!
Well, they're all squabbling.
Calliope takes the lead!
Yes! Die!
That's so dying.
Ugh, shit!
No! Not every time! You can't get it every time, Kronii!
Ugh! Points!
Come on!
Hey! Let me—
Ugh!
Have this one!
Time's up!
No!
Oh yoi yoi!
That's so tired!
Yo, why are y'all so strong?
I don't get it.
I'm dead.
Are you good? Are you good?
We are good.
Oh god, okay, so good.
Man, I feel like we just had a... came out of a battle.
I'm dead.
Raora!
I'm good.
Ii shoubu.
Good match.
That's what I call 'ii shoubu'.
That's what I call a good match.
Okay, okay.
How was it?
Yo, how do you guys think you did?
I think I won.
Me too.
No, no, no, no. I think Kronii won.
With the sheer force of her muscles pushing people out of the way!
I'm so sorry! And it wasn't even that!
She could not be pushed—
I mean, hey, you know what? Competitive spirit,
I can't even argue with that.
Well done, well done, everyone.
Well done.
Well, let's see how that weighs up against the results, shall we?
Yay!
I bet I am the winner.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! I'm the winner!
Yes, Kronii, we get it, you win.
Me, me, me, me!
Yes, Kronii, we get it! You win!
All right, all right, let's see how we all did then. Here we go.
Okay, drum roll please.
Drum roll.
Winner is...
Kronii!
Yay! Kronii won! Woo!
That crazy clock, she's too strong.
Man! Congratulations, Kronii!
Congrats! Congrats! I knew it! I knew it anyway!
Thank you, thank you.
There was no defeating the clock of steel, oh man!
This is rich!
It's rich!
She's too good, Raora! She can't be beaten!
I tried to pick her up and move her, but you just can't be- she can't be moved! She's immovable!
I tried to pick her up and move her, but you just can't be— she can't be moved! She's immovable!
Oh! Man, it's really too bad though.
I was gonna give you the ticket if you managed to win, but oh well!
This round's a bust! All boo-hoo, so sad! Oh, I cry!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a second! There must be a way, right? I- I need the ticket!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a second! There must be a way, right? I— I need the ticket!
I need to clear the game!
I mean—
Please, please! It's not- it's not up to me.
Please, please! It's not— it's not up to me.
I mean—
Please, please!
It's not up to me, but you know what? What to do, what to do?
I feel kind of bad, you're my cute kohai.
Korone-senpai, Korone-senpai, doushite ii?
Yeah, so ne...
Do you like Japanese TV show?
Yes! I love Japanese TV show, yes.
Um... please cute one-gai!
Eh? One-gai?
Kawaii one-gai?
You want me to beg?
Yeah!
One-gai? Ah, please, uh, this—
Use this camera, okay? This camera...
Chotto hikui, chotto hikuku, chotto hikuku.
A bit too low?
Okay, we'll make it better. Okay.
Up, up eyes! Up eyes, okay?
Komorebi?
Cute the face, cute the face, okay?
I can't wait! Okay, ganba, ganba! One-gai!
Raora's Cute Plea!
[Title: Raora's Cute Plea!]
Uh, three, two, one, action!
Please! Please, Korone-senpai! Please, one-gai! Please, I need the ticket! Please, I need the ticket! Please, please, Korone-senpai, I beg you! Please! Please! Give me the ticket!
Oh man, I feel so bad now.
I need the ticket!
Koko made yaru to wa... Is my 3D dead?
All right, all right, since she's done and you've done—
Sonna ni hoshii no ne?
All right, all right, all right, Raora, you've done it! You got the ticket! Look at your hand! Look at your hand!
Got the ticket!!
Yatta! Getto one-gai!
Okay, okay, all right! Good job! I got the ticket! Let's go!
Well done! See, no problem! Happy ending!
You will receive the jetpack Chachini if you gather up three tickets! Count 'em! Three! So, good luck on the next games as well!
Thank you, senpai! Thank you!
Yeah! No problem! Tickets awry!
Now go do your best! Okay, do your best! Thank you so much!
Go sleigh! Go sleigh! Yes! Slay!
Please wait, go straight.
Go straight, this way, this way!
This way, go straight!
I go.
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! See ya!
Oh my gosh, this area is really different from the last one!
It's super dark, and look at all the bars!
Is this, is this kind of scary?
Hold on.
What is that?
I hear voices!
Is that ghosts?
What is that?
Oh my gosh!
To get you!
Please Kenny!
Please, my time has come!
Please take my soul!
Is that ghosts, or is that Nerissa and Moona?
Yeah, you're going to say you don't recognize us?
Of course I recognize you!
Congratulations on your 3D!
Thank you!
I'm finally...
I think we have to introduce.
Of course.
Starting from me.
Hello everyone, I am Moona Hoshinova from Hololive Indonesia Generation 1!
Hi darlings, this is Hololive English Advent's devilish diva, the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft!
Thank you for loving me!
Thank you so much for being here!
We come here to bring a game!
A game?
Yes, really?
It's in full cooperation!
A co-op?
That's good.
Uh what what we're gonna do? What we're gonna do?
Well, the game this time is... 1, 2, 3! Limbo Dance! Panthera!
The rules are super simple.
The three of us are gonna do some sexy limbo dance! Dancing, yes, the limbo dance, dancing as we make our way towards the stage! Yay!
So excited! Me too!
And once we're there, there's one thing left to do: We're all gonna sing a super awesome trio song! So happy!
Sounds simple, right?
Sounds simple, let's see.
I am I'm born for this. Let's go!
But, you know, are we really going to be able to do this?
I think we might have not thought ahead too far.
Of course we're gonna do it!
No, but you know, we all have something that I feel like will make limbo a little bit difficult.
Something that is really really hard, but it's fun!
Save it for the game, you ladies! Okay.
Let's do it!
First off though, we need to do some workouts.
Oh!
Yes!
Yes! Keep going, girls!
Yeah, let's warm up a little bit before the game, then!
Right! That's us ready all to go!
Yeah!
I took off my jacket because it's so hot in here!
Can you do me a favor? Of course!
Could you jump a little bit more?
Just a little bit! Just a little bit! Yes, you want us to jump, so let's go! A lot of jumping, so let's go!
And look at those shoulders, too! Show those off! Very nice! Thank you!
Thank you!
Oh my god! I'm gonna do my very best in limbo dance!
Yes! Let's do it then! Let's get the music going!
Are you ready?
I'm ready! It's your 3D reunion, so get going!
Well, that's too easy for me. Are you guys ready?
Yes!
Okay, here we go!
Yay! Good job!
I'm going next!
Moona! Too easy for her!
Yes! Nerissa!
Nerissa, you can do it! Oh my goodness!
Easy peasy!
Who's next? Same order?
Same order, let's keep it going a little bit more fair!
Well, I'm gonna do it, then!
Now show us how it's done!
Good job!
Okay, I can do it. Easy, easy!
Look at you go!
Okay, Nerissa, Nerissa! Oh! Easy game!
Hey, this one's a little bit more difficult! Maybe some fire order?
先輩、おっと。
Senpai, whoops.
私がやってあげるよ。
I'll do it for you.
オッケー。
Okay.
おっ、おっ。
Oh, oh.
おっ、あっ、おっ、待って、待って。
Oh, ah, oh, wait, wait.
ああ、見ちゃった。
Ah, I looked.
次ね、次。
Next, next.
You can do it.
Watch how it's done.
Show me, please.
おおー！
Whoa!
That's so clean, girl.
Let's go! My turn.
Definitely gonna do it.
Come on, Kohai.
はーい！
Haah!
So good, girl!
オッケー、じゃあ、スイッチしよう。私が行くね。
Okay, then, let's switch. I'll go first.
Yes, you go first.
Oh my goodness!
She's nailing it.
Are you gonna be able to do it, Mona?
You can do it, Mona.
I believe, you can do it, you can do it.
This is the real tough one.
You can do it! Mona, Mona, Mona, Mona!
Yes, she did it!
Alright, my turn. Let me show you off my skills.
You can do it, Raora.
はーっ！おおー！おうおー！
Haa! Ohh! Whoa!
Fail? Oh, no.
Oh good, I'm good, I'm good.
You're okay, you're okay.
No, we have to keep going, you're still too close.
Keep going.
Alright, right, right... Let me, let me rise a little bit.
Oh my god, and I'm too old for this.
Come here, grandma. Come here, come here. We have this kind of ideal games, sumo lines.
2 more lines, come on, 2 more, 2 more, 2 more.
We have two more to go, right?
Wait a second. You dropped yours. Oh, no.
Well, I think I'm done with these two, then.
Oh, go for it.
I think I still can keep it for now.
Time to get serious, so I'm gonna lock in.
This is impossible, hello?
Yeah, it's a little bit low, but I think we can do it.
Okay, I'll try first.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
She's too good, Mona. I don't know how you can do it.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Come on, you can do it. You can do it. Come on, Mona, Mona, Mona!
No, I think I have an idea.
You got an idea? Wow! The power of brain.
Let's see. You can do it.
Come on, Raora, you got this. Okay.
I think I can do it.
Oh!
That's great! That's really nice.
Okay, I don't think I can... I don't know if I can do this one.
Ah, I mean, you did so good so far. You can do it!
You can do it! One more!
I think you're too tall for this one.
I'm gonna hold you.
I'm gonna fall, I'm gonna fall.
I'm gonna hold you. I'm gonna hold you.
Yeah! I did it!
I'm going to follow their way. I'm going to follow her way.
Yes. Let's do this.
Do we're gonna put it? Oh, this is getting serious.
This is getting serious.
Ho!
Oh, oh, oh, oh! Oh my goodness! Oh, my god!
Okay, okay.
Then it's my turn now. How what to do?
Well, I'm a b-cat, so
Yeah! Nya, nya, nya! Too cute to fail!
Thank you! Here you go.
Well, I still think we have one more obstacle yet before us.
Look at the slope.
Let's go! We've got to go up!
All right, everyone. Don't forget our limbo dance.
Oh, yes, limbo dance now. Let's go to stage.
Are you guys excited?
Yes! So excited!
I'm so ready!
Ooh!
Oh my god, that was so tiring.
Yeah.
But we did it. We had mistakes already.
Yeah, we here.
You're right. Here. Oh my god. We're ready for this.
Okay, I don't know what I'm doing, but let's do it.
We've got to go further. Yay!
All right. Last part.
捕まえちゃう! どこにいるの? ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ
I'm gonna catch you! Where are you? No way, no way, no matter where you are, no way!
捕まえちゃう! だれといるの? ダメよダメよ 私以外はダメよ
I'm gonna catch you! Who are you with? No way, no way, nobody other than me!
甘いよ甘い そんな装備じゃ
It's too sweet, with that kind of equipment,
逃げられるわけ無いじゃないか
There's no way you can escape, is there?
狙いをつけて 密かに
Take aim and secretly
背後から
from behind,
I love you
私のことを 好きになるはず
you should fall in love with me,
I love you
そこに正義があるの
justice exists there,
何度も言わせる つもりなの？
Do you intend to make me say it over and over?
おやまあ おやまあ
Oh my, oh my
抵抗するなら
If you're going to resist,
してごらん！
try it!
いがいに
Surprisingly,
我が儘だと 知っているけれど
I know I'm selfish,
私の方が上手なようね
But I'm better at this, right?
冷たい言葉 優しい視線 獲物は…君だよ！
Cold words, gentle gaze, the prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の 君の 心盗んでみせるよ
I'll steal your heart, your heart
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の 君の 心を離さない
I won't let go of your heart, your heart
熱いよ熱い 愛のルールは 破られるため あるんだよ
It's too hot, the rules of love exist so that they can be broken
ずるい罠へと 誘う微笑みは
The smile that lures you into a devious trap
I miss you
好きのせいだし 悪くないでしょ
it's because of my love, it's not bad, right?
I miss you
それが重度の恋よ
this is a serious love,
絶対全てをいただくよ？
Are you going to give me everything?
おやまあ おやまあ
Oh my, oh my
抵抗するなら
If you're going to resist,
してごらん！
try it!
てごわい
You're tough
偽りだって 疑うよりも
Rather than doubting that it's a lie,
私のこと 信じてみてよ
try believing in me,
優しい言葉 冷たい視線 獲物は…君だよ！
Gentle words, cold gaze, the prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 君の 瞳が欲しい
Cutie Panther, I want your eyes
私 きっと きっと盗んでみせるよ
I will definitely steal them
Cutie Panther 君の 瞳が欲しい
Cutie Panther, I want your eyes
私 きっと 素早く逃さない
I will definitely not let them escape quickly
何度も言わせる つもりなの？
Do you intend to make me say it over and over?
おやまあ おやまあ
Oh my, oh my
抵抗するなら
If you're going to resist,
してごらん！
try it!
いがいに
Surprisingly
我が儘だと 知っているけれど
I know I'm selfish
私の方が上手なようね
But I'm better at this, right?
冷たい言葉 優しい視線 獲物は…君だよ！
Cold words, gentle gaze, the prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の 君の 心盗んでみせるよ
I'll steal your heart, your heart
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の 君の 心を離さない
I won't let go of your heart, your heart
捕まえちゃう！ (どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ)
Let's catch you! Where are you? It's impossible, wherever you are!
捕まえちゃう！ (だれにいるの？ ダメよダメよ 私以外はダメよ)
Let's catch you! Who are you with? Anyone but me is no good!
捕まえちゃう！ (どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ)
Let's catch you! Where are you? It's impossible, wherever you are!
捕まえちゃう！ (だれにいるの？ ダメよダメよ 私以外はダメよ)
Let's catch you! Who are you with? Anyone but me is no good!
How was that, Velvet?
That's really nice!
That's how Velvet does it.
So cool, right?
Let's do it together! Ha-happy!
Thank you for dancing and singing with me!
And also, since we already finished our session, so here's your ticket!
Oh my gosh, I got it! Look at you, all clear!
Congratulations, Raora!
How's stuff? One more left now.
Let's go! Thank you so much, I'm so happy!
It was so fun, thank you for having us!
Thank you! Good luck getting that final ticket too, all right?
Yeah, true!
I'll do my best.
I promise, thank you girls!
You can do it!
Well, as for us, we should take our leave now.
Bye-bye!
No, we must leave!
Yes, then leave me, girl, we need to go!
No!
Oh.
The limbo danced so hard that it became their default walking state.
What is this place?
Oh my god, it seems like...
This place came out of a sci-fi movie or something like that.
But now I'm curious.
What kind of game they got prepared for me this time?
Wait a second.
I smell something dark smell.
I know who you are.
Come out, come here!
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so happy!
Your tail's looking really happy too.
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, let's talk about it.
There's a game today, right?
And that's not the game, right?
Okay, okay.
Well, why don't you guys introduce yourselves?
I know who you are!
I'm Fuwawa!
I know who you are! I'm Mococo!
Together we're FuwaMoco!
I'm not Fuwawa, no, obviously you are.
I'm Koseki Bijou, sparkling gem of Hololive English Advent!
I'm still me, Raora Panthera from Hololive English Justice, just this, this time in 3D!
Wait, have you introduced yourselves before?
I'm not sure about that, maybe.
Always good for Halloween.
It's okay, it's okay.
So, what's the last game going to be?
What about for this next game?
Actually, Raora, you are the only one in this challenge!
What do you mean?
But we have a very important role too, right?
Yeah, what are you guys going to do?
We're going to stop you!
No, no, no, no, you're going to let me win!
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
You got to let me win! It's my debut and it's the last ticket! I need it!
No, not at all!
We're going to put you through the ringer, yeah!
You're not ready to hear what the third mini-game is.
It is...
One, two, three, run, run, run!
Okay, okay, what's the rules?
Are you curious?
I'm very curious, you know.
Take a look at the conveyor belt behind you!
What is this, huh?
There is nothing on it, Debu!
Oh, hold on. If there is something on it...
Bring it out!
What is that?
Ew, is that a pizza?
Pineapple pizza!
Broken up spaghetti!
Ketchup spaghetti!
I'm done with this, I'm so done, I'm leaving.
I'm leaving!
I'm not going to play this game!
No, I'm not going to play this game.
It's too much for me!
No, it's too much for me.
I'm done with this.
Everything we brought out here is everything you hate!
To clear the stage, Raora must dodge all the incoming obstacles during the time limit!
And avoid everything that's on it!
You can do it! You can do it!
So, why you guys are here then?
What are you guys gonna do?
Well, we'll be using certain things...
...which will make life way more difficult, ya know!
You can't do this to me!
Pizza, baby!
Yeah.
No, you... you really are criminals!
Ha ha ha ha ha! Don't know.
No, no. No, you're not going to do this to me!
Well... let's go, gravel.
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, we'll be... we'll be right back. We'll be right back!
No, no, no.
Come back!
What are they gonna do?
No?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay, okay, I will play the game! I will play the game!
Okay, okay, you have to play the game! You have to play the game!
Okay, I will play the game!
Did you like that? Because there's more where that came from!
Yeah, that touched me with that onion!
It's bigger than you, Biboo!
Look at that, hold to me!
I'm bigger than this onion! This is not a normal size onion, hey!
This is a giant onion, hey!
Cucumber is good by you, um, yumm!
Woah!
Now then, let's get going here!
Let's go, bye-bye!
Oh yeah, let's go, onion! Yay!
Are you okay? I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine!
Okay!
You ready, Raora?
Um... um, not sure.
Hey, hey, hey, guys!
Why? Guys, can we play another game?
Okay, the timer... you have to survive for 60 seconds.
Okay!
If you keep dodging for 60 seconds, you'll level up, okay?
Okay, okay, okay, I'm ready.
There's a total of three levels, so try to escape to the very end without getting hit, okay?
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, then!
Okay, okay.
Here we go!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
Oh no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Look at those bottles! Ha!
Okay!
Oh no!
You missed up, you did!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
You gotta be careful, spaghetti!
Ah! No, no, no, no!
Oh, oh! Careful! Oh, my god!
This is so hard!
No, no, no, no!
Okay, no, no, no, no!
Hey, watch out! Watch out!
Oh, watch out! Watch out! Watch out!
You have to stay! Be careful!
Be careful! Be careful! Watch out! Watch out!
Be careful! Be careful!
Failed, your game!
Yeah! Biboo!
You want to try again? One more time!
Let's do it more!
Watch out! Watch out!
Yay!
How it feels?
Maybe it were a bit too hard out there. That felt like a long time.
Yeah, definitely.
It was definitely hard.
Okay, then we're going to set the clock to 30 seconds.
That's how we fail!
Okay, let's do it then!
Okay, I can definitely make it.
Okay, we're going to go again!
Three,
two,
one!
Game start!
I'm not going to die!
Oh, careful! Oh, careful!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, you cute! You cute! You cute! You cute!
Oh, you cute! You cute!
No, no, no, no!
Oh, watch out! Watch out!
Oh, so box so young! So!
No, no, no, no! Watch out! Watch out!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Clear!
Level one, clear!
You did it! You did it!
That took good a deal!
You think you could do go though?
Yeah, that was just level one.
You have level two now!
That was too easy, you know?
Oh, okay. Wow!
Let's try level two then!
Okay, okay, you can do it!
Is this level two for a time?
Yeah, let's do it! Oh, my god!
Yay!
Level two, go!
Stop!
Game start!
Okay, let's go!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no! Get down, get down!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
No, no, no, no, no! Get down, get down!
I didn't do it for clear!
I am so good at holding your hands!
You know, you're not getting kind of are you?
Not slowing down or anything, huh?
Well, you know, maybe you didn't put enough effort.
Oh yeah? Okay!
Well, we're gonna make it harder then!
Let's get ready for...
Level 3! Yeah! Level 3!
The ticket is mine!
Here we go to the next level, but I think...
this one's going to be extra hard!
Because you said that we weren't trying hard.
You know what we're going to do?
We're going to make this one, you only have one try!
And you know what? That's not all,
it's going to be extra hard!
This is not fair at all!
You guys are cheating!
This is not fair! This is a game!
You guys better prepare yourself!
You guys better prepare yourselves!
Okay, level 3!
Let's go! Game start!
Okay!
Yoshi! Well, really, I don't think she's going to be able to come back from that!
Alright! Well, really, I don't think she's going to be able to come back from that!
No, it's over! Baw-baw-bye!
Game over!
Ha! Oh! No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay, okay, it's okay!
Well, you know guys, today is my treaty debut, right?
So maybe, you know, sempais, you guys could give me the tickets anyway?
No!
No! No! No! No! No!
No! You'll never get the tickets!
I'm not getting the tickets?
No, no tickets for you! Sorry!
No!
Raora, we have prepared a special stage for you!
Really?
Yeah! You know, well, it was fun, you know, torturing you with things you hate. That was really fulfilling!
You know, we kind of want to see your cool side.
My cool side?
You really want to see my cool side? Show it all to everyone!
Yeah! Maybe you can put all those angry feelings and exalts! Yes! Sing! Yes!
Okay! Okay! Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
もう行け場がないわ
There's nowhere left to go anymore,
この恋の熱量
the heat of this love.
ah...
灰色の雲 モノクロの喧騒
Grey clouds, the monochrome clamor
日差しはかげり
Sunlight casts a shadow...
The sunlight casts a shadow,
夕暮れは色を変えていく
and the twilight changes color.
呼応 世界がにじんで
The world blurs,
それでも好きでいられるかなんて
but can I still love you even so?
わかってる けどどうすればいいの
I know that, but what should I do?
どうしたら どうすれば
What can I do, what should I do?
バカだな 私……
I'm such an idiot...
始めるのよ これは戦争
Let's start, this is war!
嬉しそうなきみをみるなんて
Seeing you looking so happy...
切なる恋 それは罪
Ardent love is a sin.
見せてあげる 私の想いを
I'll show you my feelings!
叫んでみたメガホンは壊れてたの
The megaphone I shouted into broke.
どれだけ背伸びしたって君の視界に入らない
No matter how on my tiptoes I am, I won't enter your field of vision.
呼応 いつの間にか晴れた空
The sky cleared up before I knew it.
全然似合わない気持ちが抑えられなくて
I can't hold back these totally unfitting feelings—
どうしたら どうすれば
What should I do, what should I do?
泣いてなんか ないんだからね
It's not like I'm crying or anything!
大好き
I love you.
たたかうのよ
I'm going to fight!
ハートを撃て 手段なんて選んでられない
Shoot for the heart, I can't afford to choose my methods.
スカートひらり 見せつけるのよ 君の視線 奪ってみせるの
My skirt flutters as I show it off, I'll steal your gaze!
迎撃用意 戦況は未だ不利なのです
Prepare to intercept, the battle situation is still unfavorable.
恋は盲目 君の口づけで目が覚めるの！
Love is blind, your kiss wakes me up!
Oh... I'm sorry, Chattino!
I tried my best, but I only got two!
Noooo... my jetpack...
The jetpack exploded!
I'm sorry, Chattino.
Actually, I have a present for all of you!
Present? I wonder what it is? Is it a cucumber?
Uh-uh, let me tell you. Good girl.
That's the best! It's not a jetpack, but it's really nice!
Thanks, Chattino!
Well then, before I reveal the best present ever, I've got an announcement to make!
Ta-da! Raora Panthera Pencil Case & Keychain!
Yes! This is a cute pencil case with me in our Chattino costume.
So I hope you guys can bring it everywhere, it's cool in the office, literally everywhere! So please don't miss out, okay?
So I hope you guys can bring it everywhere—in the office, literally everywhere! So please don't miss out, okay?
Ah, that was such a fun 3D showcase with a lot of things happening!
Did everyone have fun, Chattini? Did you guys have fun?
Ah... Thank you, I'm so happy to hear that! Thank you!
Since like you guys had a great time with me today, I'm so happy, thank you! I'll keep doing my best to bring fun streams and more 3D live performances like this one today, okay?
Since you guys had such a great time with me today, I'm so happy, thank you! I'll keep doing my best to bring fun streams and more 3D live performances like this one today, okay?
I appreciate you guys so much. Thank you, Chattini, for all your support! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Finally!
It's the longer-awaited present from me to everyone!
It's the long-awaited present from me to everyone!
Are you guys ready?
The present is...
my first original song!
I'm so happy! It's full of things I like and so many personal touches.
I worked really, really hard on this song, so I hope you guys're gonna take a listen to it, okay?
I worked really hard on this song, so I hope you guys are gonna take a listen, okay?
Are you guys ready? Are you guys excited?
Let's go to the stage!
Gacha×Gacha ADVENTURE!
(はい！はい！はい！Pon！Pon！)
(Yes! Yes! Yes! Pon! Pon!)
(Gacha, Gacha, RAOOOOO!!)
さあ、さあ、お宝探しだ
Come on, come on, let's go treasure hunting!
「今日は、ど～んな獲物が見つかるかニャ？」
"What kind of loot will we find today?"
ほら、ほら、みんなも一緒に「楽しい冒険、しゅっぴ～っ！」
Look, look, everyone together, "Let's set off on a fun adventure!"
(Un！Due！Tre！)
(Un! Due! Tre!)
ハマっちゃったら抜け出せないの～
If you get hooked, you won't be able to get out~
食べ物ぬいぐるみ pizzaもpastaも全部
Food, stuffed animals, pizza, pasta, everything
詰め込んだ魅惑の迷宮 ワクワク止まらない
A labyrinth filled with charm, the excitement doesn't stop!
(Proviamo！)
(Proviamo!)
取れそうで取れなくてイライラ クレーンゲーム
It's frustrating that it seems easy but isn't, crane game!
「にゃ～もう！」
"Nya~ enough!"
諦めたままリタイア するはずないじゃない！「目指せコンプリート！」
Giving up and retiring is out of the question! "Aim to complete!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ♪
Come on, one more time, it's useless even if you stop it♪
もう一回 繰り返すデジャヴ 諦めろって言わないで
One more time, déjà vu repeating, don't tell me to give up
三度目の正直 だから無問題 溢れる想いがとらんなに
Third time's the charm, so no problem, the overflowing feelings I can't stop
これって天職！？
Is this my calling!?
楽しいことで満たされている この先もずっと「はい、せーのっ」 Gacha×Gacha ADVENTURE!
Filled with fun things, always from here on out, "Yes, one, two!" Gacha×Gacha ADVENTURE!
(ガチャ...ガチャ...ガチャ...ガチャ...)
(Gacha... Gacha... Gacha... Gacha...)
「ゲーム、リスタート！」
"Game, restart!"
グルグル回しまくっちゃえ 「ダメだ...止まんない！」
Spin and spin it around, "It's no good... I can't stop!"
お目当ての獲物が出るまで 「お願い...もう一回！」
Until I get the loot I'm aiming for, "Please... one more time!"
(Bim bum bam！)
(Bim bum bam!)
ビートに乗ったら止まれないの～ 音ゲーもお手のもの
Once I get on the beat, I can't stop~ Rhythm games are easy for me
comboもfeverも全部 キメたら完璧Groove！ ズレたらゲームオーバーさ
Combo, fever, everything, if I nail it, a perfect groove! If off, game over!
(Andiamo！)
(Andiamo!)
レースゲームエンジン全開でアチアチ 白熱バトル！「いけいけGo！Go！Go！」
Racing game, engine full throttle, getting hot, intense battle! "Go, go, go!"
コーナーで差をつけてら 目指すは1位だー！
If I pull ahead in the corner, I'm aiming for 1st place!
さあ、もう一回でも今日は終わり もう一回言いかけて止まる
Come on, one more time, but today is the end. One more time, starting to say it and stopping.
楽しかった気持ちが 胸をキュっとするの
The fun feelings make my chest tight.
ねぇねぇ、もうバイバイしなきゃダメ？ まだ帰りたくない これって恋かな！？
Hey, hey, do I have to say bye-bye already? I don't want to go home yet, is this love!?
ワクワクで満ち溢れたこの先のの日々も「一緒に冒険しよう！」
Filled with excitement, the days ahead too, "Let's go on an adventure together!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ もう一回 繰り返すデジャヴ 諦めろって言わないで
Come on, one more time, it's useless. One more time, déjà vu, don't give up
何度でもチャレンジ だから無問題 溢れる想いがとらんなに これこそ天職！！ 何度でもやり直せる
Challenge as many times! No problem, I can't stop. Calling!! I can redo it!
そう人生は (みんなも一緒に！)
That's what life is (Everyone together too!)
Gacha×Gacha ADVENTURE!
(はい！はい！はい！Pon！Pon！)
(Yes! Yes! Yes! Pon! Pon!)
(Gacha, Gacha, RAOOOOO!!)
「また一緒に冒険しようね！Ciao ciao♪」
"Let's go on an adventure together again! Ciao ciao♪"
That was so much fun!
How did you like it, Chattini? Did you like it?
Thank you for watching and listening!
Today was so much fun. Thank you so much, everyone, for all your support!
I can't wait to see you all again! Until next time!
Ciao ciao!
Big cat means big trouble!